Hello and welcome to the Complete Python Bootcamp.
-: Ol e seja bem vindo ao Complete Python Bootcamp.
My name is Jose Portilla,
Meu nome  Jose Portilla,
and I will be your instructor for this course.
e eu serei seu instrutor para este curso.
I've taught thousands of students
Eu ensinei milhares de alunos
on Udemy about data science,
na Udemy sobre cincias dos
and I'm excited to teach even more students
dados, e estou ansioso para ensinar
about the complete ins and outs
ainda mais alunos sobre os
of the Python programming language.
inteiros e integrados completos da linguagem de programao Python.
This course is designed to take you from zero
Este curso  projetado para lev-lo
to hero in Python in an easy and fun fashion.
de zero para heri em Python de forma fcil e divertida.
So why learn Python?
Ento, por que aprender Python?
Python is one of the most useful
Python  uma das linguagens
programming languages to know,
de programao mais teis para conhecer,
and in recent years,
e nos ltimos anos,
skill demand for Python has exploded in the job market.
a demanda de habilidades para Python explodiu no mercado de trabalho.
With this course, it's easy to learn
suas prprias idias com o Python.
and it's a very powerful tool
Com este curso,
for implementing your own ideas with Python.
fcil de aprender e  uma ferramenta muito poderosa para implementar
So who is this course for?
Ento, para quem  esse curso?
This course is suitable for
Este curso
beginners that have never programmed,
adequado para iniciantes que nunca foram programados,
programmers coming in from another language,
programadores que entram de outro idioma e,
and finally,
finalmente, programadores que
programmers who know the basics of Python syntax
conhecem o bsico da sintaxe de Python, mas
but want to bring their knowledge to the next level
querem trazer seus conhecimentos para
with the advanced topics presented in this course.
o prximo nvel com os tpicos avanados apresentados neste curso.
So, what's the course like?
Ento, como  o curso?
We'll start off by getting Python up
Comecemos por colocar o Python
and running on your computer,
em funcionamento no seu
regardless of your operating system.
computador, independentemente do seu sistema operacional.
Whether you're using Windows, Mac or Linux.
Se voc est usando Windows, Mac ou Linux.
Then you'll get lifetime access to over 100 lectures,
bsica de Python, at os tpicos e mdulos avanados em Python.
discussing everything from basic Python syntax,
Ento voc ter acesso  vida a mais
to the advanced topics and modules in Python.
de 100 palestras, discutindo tudo, desde a sintaxe
Each lecture includes a video screencast
Cada palestra inclui um screencast
with clear concept explanations,
de vdeo com explicaes de
as well as entire notebooks filled with both code
conceito claro, bem como cadernos inteiros preenchidos
and written explanations.
com cdigo e explicaes escritas.
So you can learn in whatever way is best for you.
Ento, voc pode aprender da maneira que for melhor para voc.
There's tests, quizzes, and homework assignments
do caminho para verificar sua compreenso.
all along the way to check your understanding.
H testes, questionrios e trabalhos de casa ao longo
This course is also project-based with milestone projects
Este curso tambm  baseado em projetos com
where you will create games with Python,
projetos de marco onde voc criar
including a final capstone project.
jogos com Python, incluindo um projeto de capstone final.
You'll also learn how to avoid commoner mistakes in Python,
Voc tambm aprender a evitar erros comuns em
and learn best programming practises,
Python e aprender as melhores prticas
such as code formatting and object-oriented programming.
de programao, como formatao de cdigo e programao orientada a objetos.
Once you complete this course,
Python no seu currculo.
you'll feel extremely confident putting
Uma vez que voc completar este
Python programming on your resume.
curso, voc se sentir extremamente confiante colocando a programao
More importantly, you'll learn to have
Mais importante ainda, voc aprender a
a lifelong love of programming,
ter um amor ao longo da programao, e
and there's a 30 day money back guarantee.
h uma garantia de reembolso de dinheiro de 30 dias.
If you're unsatisfied in any way,
Se voc no est satisfeito de
you get your money back, no questions asked.
qualquer forma, voc recebe o seu dinheiro de volta, sem perguntas.
You'll also be able to keep the over 100 lecture notes
como um agradecimento por experimentar o curso.
as a thank you for trying out the course.
Voc tambm poder manter as mais de 100 notas de conferncia
Check out the next preview video
Confira o prximo vdeo de visualizao
for a full curriculum overview of the entire course.
para uma viso geral do currculo completo de todo o curso.
So what are you waiting for?
Ento, o que voc est esperando?
Enrol in the course today
Inscreva-se no curso
and learn the power of Python Programming.
hoje e aprenda o poder da programao de Python.